<?xml version="1.0"?>
<question id="EM_46" module="EM">
  <questionText>Describe how you can tell the difference between the crystals from the calcite test and salt crystals when you observe them in an evaporation dish.</questionText>
  <referenceAnswers>
    <referenceAnswer id="EM_46-a1">The crystals have different shapes. Salt crystals are square with little Xs. The calcite crystals are shaped like needles (long and skinny).</referenceAnswer>
  </referenceAnswers>
  <studentAnswers>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.137.1" accuracy="incorrect">It if looks like salt then the salt is salt crystals. If it has lines in them it is calcite crystals.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.141.1" accuracy="incorrect">Calcite is straight lines.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.147.1" accuracy="correct">The calcite crystals have lines. Salt crystal have squares.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.149.1" accuracy="correct">The calcite crystals were lines and the salt crystals were pyramids and squares.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.153.1" accuracy="correct">You can tell them apart because the calcite is just lines. The salt crystals were pyramids and squares.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.281.1" accuracy="incorrect">Calcite look like this the salt, drew picture, crystals look like this, drew picture.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.284.1" accuracy="incorrect">Salt crystals had an X on them and calcite crystals do not.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.288.1" accuracy="incorrect">The salt crystals look like squares.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.356.1" accuracy="incorrect">The salt crystals were square and the calcite had stripes.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.383.1" accuracy="incorrect">When the crystals of the mock rock you could see them really good and with the minerals, calcite, they were hard to see.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.397.1" accuracy="incorrect">I know that crystals are different than salt crystals because the salt crystals do not have needle like structures.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.399.1" accuracy="incorrect">They both have different crystals in them, the ones that are white are whiter than the calcite test crystals.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.406.1" accuracy="correct">The calcite crystals looked liked small white needles, the salt crystals were small white globs and squares with Xs and diamonds.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.409.1" accuracy="incorrect">Well the vinegar if you beating a rock it will store bowl.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.422.1" accuracy="correct">The crystals were points and the salt crystal were Xs.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.428.1" accuracy="incorrect">The salt crystals have Xs and the others do not.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.431.1" accuracy="incorrect">One of them was whiter than the other and had more crystals.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.432.1" accuracy="incorrect">I can tell the difference because calcite crystals spread out and salt crystals look like squares.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.433.1" accuracy="incorrect">The salt crystals have Xs in them and the other ones look different.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.491.1" accuracy="incorrect">They are different because crystals from the calcite test are not minerals and the salt crystals are minerals.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.494.1" accuracy="correct">I can they are different because of their shape calcite crystals look like needles and salt had squares with Xs inside them.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.508.1" accuracy="incorrect">The salt crystals have little Xs and are square shape.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.523.1" accuracy="incorrect">Because the salt crystals were squares with Xs in them and the calcite crystals were and did not make shapes.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.557.1" accuracy="incorrect">The crystals have Xs inside when calcite has like white spot.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.561.1" accuracy="incorrect">The calcite can be white and crystals is black.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.572.1" accuracy="incorrect">Salt crystals had Xs and the crystals did not.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.576.1" accuracy="incorrect">The crystals did not look much like calcite but the did not look like salt either.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.599.1" accuracy="correct">Because the crystals from the calcite test were long and skinny. The salt crystals were fat and had designs on.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.605.1" accuracy="correct">The calcite crystals had tall needle patterns and the salt crystals were squares with Xs in them.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.607.1" accuracy="incorrect">The difference is the mineral have a little X in the rock have more color.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.609.1" accuracy="correct">Because the crystals from calcite look like little needles and the salt crystals had squares with Xs on them.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.615.1" accuracy="incorrect">The one has Xs is the one look like sauce.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.626.1" accuracy="incorrect">Calcite crystals, salt crystals, acid, vinegar.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.630.1" accuracy="incorrect">A crystal is signet, and has stuff in the middle. The calcite is clear smooth. Salt crystals look like something is dried up.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.634.1" accuracy="incorrect">If you have a bowl and inside there is a crystal and you put vinegar in the bowl if it has calcite it will look like needles with salt it will look like yes.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="EM.46.649.1" accuracy="incorrect">Calcite crystals, long needles. Salt crystals, X shape.</studentAnswer>
  </studentAnswers>
</question>
