<?xml version="1.0"?>
<question id="PS_45b" module="PS">
  <questionText>Nathaniel and Sammy are trying to make up a code for sending messages to each other by dropping items in a drop chamber and listening to them. Sammy wants to design a code using blocks made of plastic, metal, and wood. Nathaniel thinks it would be a better idea to use wooden blocks of different sizes and shapes. Which student's method would make it easier to tell the difference between the sounds? Why?</questionText>
  <referenceAnswers>
    <referenceAnswer id="PS_45b-a1">Sammy's. Different materials would make very different sounds. Different size wood would make very similar sounds.</referenceAnswer>
  </referenceAnswers>
  <studentAnswers>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.101.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - Because a wooden blocks, because if you drop 3 thing you can not hear all 3. But if you drop one thing you can hear better.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.104.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - If it will be soft or low or high or low the pitch will be different sound! Some will be loud or low!</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.107.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - I picked Nathaniel because he has wood only. And Sammy has plastic metal and wood.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.110.1" accuracy="incorrect">Daniel - Because he dropped a popsicle.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.111.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - I picked Nathaniel because a wooden blocks has a low sound and Sammy wants to use blocks made of plastic, metal, and wood. And the objects will make a low sound.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.114.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because the metal and wood makes a louder sound kind of like vibration.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.116.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - Nathaniel is using block because the block are bigger to drop in the chamber to play.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.118.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - Because it is harder than made of plastic.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.138.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because plastic, wood and metal do not sound the same.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.141.1" accuracy="incorrect">Because what if there is only one metal item and you drop it and you hear metal.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.142.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because if they are the same material you would have to figure what size it was and which one it was, you would be able to tell easier if it was plastic, metal, or wood.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.145.1" accuracy="correct">Sammy - Because if it was same blocks just different sizes you would not know which sound it was so makes it harder but with Sammy idea they would be different so that is easy so Sammy.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.146.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because it is different material and it is easier and it is easier because if it was Nathaniel's it would be harder because it is the same material and it all sounds alike.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.152.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - Nathaniel's because it is wood and it is different sizes.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.154.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because they are not the same material.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.157.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Sammy it would be easier because plastic is difference to wood.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.160.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammys - Because there are different sounds with Sammy's idea.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.171.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel's - Because they all sound the same.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.172.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because the plastic, metal wood might sound different!</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.175.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because they are different things.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.176.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy's - Sammy's because they are all different.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.181.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because Sammy's idea is better because Sammy is different kind of blocks and Nathaniel is just one kind of block but they are different size.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.183.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - Because metal is close to the same sound of the other metals.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.185.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - Because it is wood.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.189.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because plastic, metal, and wood have different sounds so it will be easier.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.192.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because Sammy's idea would be easier than Nathaniel's idea.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.193.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy's - Sammy's, they are made out of different things.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.194.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - I think because his has these things wooden, blocks.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.195.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - Nathaniel because, Sammy is softer, and if the plastic is too soft, it will not make a sound, and he or her will not be able to hear it.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.212.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - Because wood all sounds the same but different sizes. Like a big wood and small piece kind of sound the same.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.217.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because the blocks are made of different material.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.221.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because those are all different materials.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.222.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - Because plastic and metal make different noises than just wood.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.223.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy's idea - Because using things all made of wood would be harder to discriminate.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.225.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because plastic, metal, and wood has different sounds and just wood would make the same sound.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.230.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because if you used blocks made of plastic metal and wood because it would make a differing noise so it would be easier to know.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.255.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because if you have different objects for different words it would make more sense.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.261.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - Because a big triangle block would sound the same as a little square block.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.263.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy's - Because they sound different.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.313.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because wood blocks of different shapes and sizes would sound the same so Sammy's is better.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.319.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because you could get down easy.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.320.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - Because it is all the same thing.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.322.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because you need difference thing.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.323.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because you know that metal and wood and plastic is better than Nathaniel.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.325.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because Nathaniel is not the same sizes and Sammy's will.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.328.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - I think that it would be easier to to tell apart plastic metal, and wood because metal makes a metallic sound plastic makes a clicky sound and wood blocks make a bangy sound.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.329.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy's - The all wood would just sound the same.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.331.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Why I think Sammy's idea is better because you can tell if you drop metal in the.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.333.1" accuracy="correct">Sammy - Sammy's method because if we use wood blocks of different sizes then some of the block could sound the same and wood, metal, plastic sound different.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.384.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - Because Nathaniel wants to put blocks of different sizes and it will make a different sound by the length.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.391.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Sammy's idea would be much more easier because if you did it with shapes and sizes it would be hard to hear.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.400.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy's - Nathaniel's idea would not work because it is the same material, wood that would make the same sound. Sammy's idea would work because there is different materials.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.401.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because metal, wood and plastic make different sounds.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.452.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy's - Because Sammy's idea uses different materials with different sounds. But Nathaniel uses the same materials with the same sounds.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.454.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because plastic, metal, and wood is different.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.455.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Sammy's idea is easier because if they are using different materials and Nathaniel's idea is only using wood, then you can not really tell them apart even if they are different sizes.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.459.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy's - Because the materials he mentioned were all different. So if they are all different you can tell the difference between them.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.461.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because if it were all the same material it would all sound the same but Sammy used different materials to make things sound different.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.464.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because they all do not sound the same.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.466.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because a material has a sound. Like cardboard makes a thump and metal makes a ring. So since Sammy has different material, we could discriminate thing easier.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.468.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Sammy because wooden blocks will make the same sound and Sammy's code will work because plastic, metal and wood will not make the same sound.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.469.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy's - Because Sammy's method uses different kinds of blocks and it is easy to discriminate things made of different things than discriminate things all made of one thing.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.486.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - One is made out of wood and the different material.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.488.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because metal makes a very loud sound.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.490.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - I thought Sammy's idea was easier because different sizes and shapes is harder.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.491.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because they are made out of different stuff.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.494.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because they are different things so you can tell what they are because they are different and just wood kind of makes the same sound.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.495.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - I think, Sammy because it has different materials and different sounds.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.497.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Sammy got metal stuff.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.499.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - I chose Sammy because you can tell the difference of plastic metal blocks of wood.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.501.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Sammy is easier to tell the difference because it made it out of different thing.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.502.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because if you put just wood stuff you will not be able to tell what it is.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.504.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - It is Sammy.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.505.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - Because bigger stuff wood blocks.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.508.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - Because the thing will be big or small.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.524.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because they are all different kinds of material.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.526.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because they all are different sound with Sammy but Nathaniel make all the same sounds.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.528.1" accuracy="incorrect">Because Sammy used lots of different objects, plastic, metal, wood, Nathaniel thinks you should use the same object, just different shapes.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.531.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because it is all kinds of stuff and Nathaniel is all wood it is hard to tell.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.532.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Sammy's is easier because Sammy's idea has metal, plastic, and wood so it would be easier to discriminate the properties of the objects.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.533.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because plastic, metal, and wood are different materials. And Nathaniel's code would be harder.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.536.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - Because they are all different shapes and sizes so they are easier to discriminate.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.537.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy's - Because the blocks are made of different things instead of just wood and wood sounds the same.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.539.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because Sammy has all different things. And it is easy to discriminate.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.557.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because they to are not the same sounds.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.562.1" accuracy="incorrect">Both - Because wooden blocks are just like Sammy's blocks.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.563.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because they all sound different and blocks sound the same.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.567.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because Sammy idea is right different sounds is different thing and makes the other person do not know it.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.571.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy's - I choose Sammy's because the sounds sound different.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.572.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - I think Sammy is better because it make a really hard code. Nathaniel does not makes a hard code.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.574.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - If you do not know what the thing then you need.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.593.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because he uses a lot of different items.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.595.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because you can tell the difference of metal, plastic, and wood. You know it is ding for metal and bom for plastic and hock for wood.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.596.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - I choose Nathaniel because his idea sounds better than Sammy's because using other kinds of block might be a bad idea.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.599.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy's - Sammy's method is easier because plastic, metal, and wood sound different and Nathaniel's method is not that easy because she is using wood and sound the same.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.600.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because if you know the sound that you hear it before.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.602.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Sammy will make it easier because you can tell the sound of blocks and the sound of metal.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.603.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because when you drop something in the drop chamber it will be making sound.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.605.1" accuracy="correct">Sammy - Sammy's idea is much easier because the method is made of metal, wood, plastic. But Nathaniel is all wood, even though the shapes are different it would be the same sound and will be complicated for Sammy to guess. So I think Sammy's idea is much easier.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.607.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy's - Because if you use wooden blocks, then it all sound the same and it is difficult to tell which is which.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.610.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy's - Because you are going to hear the difference easier.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.626.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - Because it would be easier to use different shapes and sizes to detect sounds.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.629.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because with this method you can get used to sounds.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.633.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because they are different and different material.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.642.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because he wanted to use plastic, metal, and wood.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.643.1" accuracy="incorrect">Sammy - Because you could know what is the difference of sounds.</studentAnswer>
    <studentAnswer id="PS.45b.644.1" accuracy="incorrect">Nathaniel - Because wood is one material wood, plastic and other materials.</studentAnswer>
  </studentAnswers>
</question>
